I'm Rowan Bullard, and I lead the AI
research team here at Tesla. I want to
tell you about an event we're running on
Tuesday, September 29th at the Tesla
offices about agentic ROI. Basically,
you've now got agentic engineering, and
you've got all these agents running in
production with all your human engineers
as well. How do you effectively evaluate
the ROI from investing in zero [music]
models, investing in the agents itself,
versus investing in the supporting
infrastructure that surrounds those
models? The context, the evals, the
verification, all of the tooling that
you've built up over time to support
human engineers, but also now agent
engineers. [music]
We'll be here in person at the Tesla
offices on Tuesday, September 29th.
We'll also be running a live stream for
if you can attend virtually. Looking
forward to talking to you all on the
29th. Register below for either in
person or virtual access.
>> [music]